today we'll talk about how to make
今天我们将讨论如何制作
machines see computer vision and we'll
机器看到计算机视觉， 我们会
present Thank You Claire said yes and
谢谢Claire 说是的和
today we will present a competition that
今天我们将举办一场比赛
unlike deep traffic which is designed to
不像设计的深度交通
explore ideas teach you about concepts
探索想法教你概念
of deep reinforcement learning seg fuse
深层强化学习seg融合
the deep dynamic driving scene
深层动态驾驶场景
segmentation competition that I'll
细分竞争，我会
present today is at the very cutting
今天的礼物正处于切入阶段
edge whoever does well in this
无论谁在这方面做得好
competition is likely to produce a
竞争很可能产生一个
publication or ideas that would lead the
出版物或想法将导致
world in the area of perception perhaps
也许是感知领域的世界
together with the people running this
和运行这个的人一起
class perhaps in your own and I
或许在 你自己和我
encourage you to do so even more cats
鼓励你这样做 更多的 猫
today computer vision today as it stands
今天的 计算机愿景如今
is deep learning majority of the
深学习多数
successes in how we interpret form
我们如何解释形式的成功
representations understand images and
表示理解图像和
videos utilize to a significant degree
影片使用的显著程度
neural networks the very ideas we've
神经网络我们的想法
been talking about that applies for
被谈论的申请
supervised unsupervised and
监督无监督和
reinforcement learning and for the
强化学习， 为
supervised case is just the focus of
监督的情况下， 是 刚刚 焦点
today the process is the same the data
今天的过程是相同 的数据
is essential there's annotated data
是必要的注释数据
where the human provides the labels that
人类提供标签的地方
serves as the ground truth in the
作为在地面真相
training process then the neural network
训练过程然后是神经网络
ghost's through that data learning to
鬼通过那个数据 学习
map from the raw sensory input to the
从原始感官输入映射到
ground truth labels and then generalize
地面真相标签，然后概括
or the testing data set and the kind of
或测试数据集和种类
raw sensors were dealing with their
原始传感器 处理 他们的
numbers I'll say this again and again
数字我会一次又一次地说这个
that for human vision for us here would
这对我们来说是人类的愿景
take for granted this particular aspect
理所当然地认为这个方面
of our ability is to take in raw sensory
我们的能力是 接受原始的感官
information through our eyes and
通过我们的眼睛 和信息
interpret
译
but it's just numbers that's something
但这只是数字而已
whether you're an expert computer vision
你是否是一个专家的计算机视觉
person or new to the field you have to
人或新的给你有到现场
always go back to meditate on is what
总是回去冥想是什么
kind of things the Machine is given what
样的事情机器给出什么
what what is the data that is tasked to
什么是任务的数据是什么
work with in order to perform the tasks
以便 执行 工作 任务
you're asking it to do
你要求它做
perhaps the data is given is highly
也许数据是高度的
insufficient to do what you want it to
不足以做你想要的
do
做
that's the question I'll come up again
这是我再次提出的问题
and again our images enough to
再次 我们的图像足够了
understand the world around you and
了解你周围的世界 ，
given these numbers the set of numbers
给出 这些 数字 的数字
sometimes with one channel sometimes
有时候有一个频道
with three RGB where every single pixel
每个像素都有三个RGB
have three different colors the task is
有三种不同的颜色任务
to classify or regress produce a
分类或回归产生a
continuous variable or one of a set of
连续变量或一 组 中 的一个
class labels as before we must be
类标签 ， 因为 我们必须 前
careful about our intuition of what is
小心我们 对什么是直觉
hard and what is easy in computer vision
计算机视觉中的难点和容易
let's take a step back to the
让我们退一步到
inspiration for neural networks our own
我们自己的神经网络 的灵感
biological neural networks because the
生物神经网络因为
human vision system and the computer
人类视觉系统和计算机
vision system is a little bit more
视觉系统更多一点
similar in these regards this
在这方面类似于此
and visual cortex is in layers and as
和视觉皮层是在层 和用作
information passes from the eyes to the
信息从 眼睛 传递到 眼睛
to the parts of the brain that makes
以使 大脑的部分
sense of the raw sensor information
原始传感器信息的 感觉
higher and higher order representations
更高阶 和更高阶的表示
have formed this is the inspiration the
已形成 这是灵感了
idea behind using deep neural networks
使用深度神经 网络背后的想法
for images higher and higher order
对于 更高和更高阶的 图像
representations of form through the
通过形式表示形式
layers there early layers taking in the
那里的早期层层
very raw and sensory information then
那么非常原始和感官信息
extracting edges connecting those edges
提取连接这些边的边
forming those edges to form more complex
形成那些边缘以形成更复杂的
features and finally into the
功能，最后进入
higher-order semantic meaning that we
我们的高阶语义意义
hope to get from these images in
希望从这些图像 中获取
computer vision deep learning is hard
计算机视觉深度学习很难
I'll say this again
我会再说一遍
the illumination variability is the
光照变化是
biggest challenge or at least one of the
最大的挑战 或至少一个
one of the biggest challenges in driving
在驾驶的最大挑战之一
for visible light cameras pose
用于可见光相机的姿势
variability the objects as I'll also
我也会改变对象的可变性
discuss about some of the advances geoff
讨论 geoff的 一些进展
hinton and the capsule networks the idea
希顿和胶囊网络 的想法
with the neural networks as they're
与神经网络一样
currently useful computer vision are not
目前有用的计算机视觉不是
good with representing variable pose
善于表示变量姿势
these objects in images and this 2d
图像中的这些对象和这个2d
plane of color and texture look very
颜色和纹理的平面看起来非常
different numerically when the object is
对象是数字上不同的
rotated and the object is mangled and
旋转，并且该对象是错位 和
shaped in different ways the deformable
以不同的方式塑造可变形的
will truncated cat intraclass
将截断 cat inraclass
variability the for the classification
分类的可变性
task which would be an example today
这个任务 今天 就是一个 例子
throughout to introduce some of the
各地要介绍一些
networks over the past decade that have
网络上 有 过去的十年
received success in some of the
一些人获得了成功
intuition and insight that made those
直觉和洞察力使这些
networks work classification there is a
网络工作分类有一个
lot of variability inside the classes
课堂内有很多变化
and very little variability between the
两者之间 的 差异很小
classes all of these are cats on top all
所有这些课程都是最重要的猫
of those are dogs are bottom they look
他们看起来是狗的底部
very different and the other I would say
非常不同，另一个 我会说
the second biggest problem in driving
驾驶中的第二大问题
perception
知觉
visible light camera perceptions
可见光相机的感知
occlusion when part of the object is
部分对象时的遮挡
occluded due to the three-dimensional
由于三维而被遮挡
nature of our world some objects in
我们这个世界的本质一些对象
front of others and they occlude the
别人面前，他们闭塞 了
background object and yet we're still
背景对象，但我们仍然
tasked with identifying the object when
负责识别对象的时间
only part of it is visible and sometimes
只有部分是可见的，有时是可见的
that part told you there's cats is very
那部分告诉你那里的猫 非常
hardly visible here
这里几乎看不到
we're tasked with classifying a cat with
我们的任务是对猫进行分类
just an ears visible just the leg and in
只有一只耳朵可以看到 腿部和 耳朵
the philosophical level as we'll talk
我们将要 谈论 的哲学层面
about the motivation for our competition
关于我们竞争的动机
here here's a cat dressed as a monkey
这里有一只打扮成猴子的猫
eating a banana on a philosophical level
在哲学 层面 上 吃香蕉
most of us understand what's going on in
我们大多数人都明白发生了什么
the scene in fact a neural network it's
事实上这是一个神经网络
to today successfully classify this
今天成功地将此分类
image this video as a cat but the
将此视频视为猫而非
context the humour of the situation and
背景情况的幽默 和
in fact you could argue it's a monkey is
事实上， 你可以说它是一只猴子
missing and what else is missing is the
缺少什么，缺少什么 是
dynamic information the temporal
动态信息的时间性
dynamics of the scene that's what's
动态的场景就是这样
missing in a lot of the perception work
在许多感知工作中缺失
that has been done to date in the
到目前为止已经完成 了
autonomous vehicle space in terms of
自动驾驶汽车空间
visible light cameras and we're looking
可见光相机，我们正在 寻找
to expand on that
扩大这一点
that's what psyche fuse is all about
这 就是灵魂融合的全部意义
image classification pipeline there's a
图像分类管道有一个
bin with different categories inside
bin里面有不同的类别
each class cat dog mug hat those bins
每一类猫狗杯子帽子那些垃圾箱
there's a lot of examples of each and
每个 和 每个都有很多例子
your task with when a new example comes
一个新的例子到来时你的任务
along you never seen before to put that
沿着你从未见过的那个
image in a bin it's the same as the
bin中的图像与它相同
machine learning tasks before and
机器学习任务 之前和
everything relies on the data that's
一切都依赖于那些数据
been ground truth that been labeled by
被 称为的基本事实
human beings
人类
amnesty is a toy data set of handwritten
大赦是手写的玩具数据集
digits often used as examples and Koko
数字经常用作例子 和 Koko
safar imagenet places and a lot of other
safar imagenet的地方和很多其他
incredible datasets rich data sets of a
令人难以置信的丰富的数据集的数据集 的
hundred thousands millions of images out
成千上万 的图像
there represent scenes people's faces
那里代表 着人们的面孔
and different objects those are all
这些都是不同的对象
ground truth data for testing algorithms
用于测试算法的地面实况数据
and for competing architectures to be
以及竞争架构
evaluated against each other see far ten
相互评估见远十
one of the simplest almost toy datasets
最简单的玩具数据集之一
of tiny icons with ten categories of
十个类别的小图标
airplane automobile bird cat deer dog
飞机汽车鸟猫鹿狗
for our course ship and truck is
对于我们的课程船和卡车是
commonly used to explore some of the
常用来探索一些
basic convolution neural networks we'll
我们将基本的卷积神经网络
discuss so let's come up with a very
讨论所以让我们想出一个非常好的
trivial classifier to explain the
琐碎的分类器来解释
concept of how we could go about it in
我们怎么能去 了解它 的概念
fact this is maybe if you start to think
事实上，这可能是你开始思考的
about how to classify an image if you
关于如何 对 图像 进行分类 的方法
don't know any of these techniques this
不知道这些 技术中的任何一种
is perhaps the approach you would take
也许 你会采取的方法
is you would subtract images so in order
你会按顺序减去图像吗？
to know that an image of a cat is
要知道猫的形象是
different than image of a dog if to
不同于狗的形象如果到
compare them when given those two images
给出这两个 图像 时比较它们
what what's the what's the way you
什么是你的方式是什么
compare them one way you could do it is
比较他们你可以做到的一种方式
you just subtract it and then sum all
你只需减去它然后总结所有
the pixel wise differences in the image
像素明智的图像差异
just subtract the intensity of the image
只是减去图像的强度
pixel by pixel sum it up if that intent
如果是那个意图 ，就像素一样加以总结
if that difference is really high that
如果这个差异 非常高
means the images are very different
指图像非常 不同
using that metric we can look at C for
使用该指标我们可以看看 C for
10 and use it as a classifier saying
10 并用它作为分类器说
based on this difference function I'm
基于这种差异功能我
going to find one of the 10 bins for a
要找到 10个箱子中的一个
new image that that is that has the
那个有新的形象
lowest difference find an image in this
最低差异在此找到一个图像
data set that is most like the image I
数据集最像图像我
have and put it in the same bin as that
把它放在同一个箱子里
images in so there's 10 classes if we
这样的图像 如果我们 有 10个班级
just flip a coin the accuracy of our
只是翻硬币我们的准确性
classifier will be 10% using our image
使用我们的图像，分类器将是 10％
difference classifier we can actually do
我们实际上可以做的差异分类器
pretty good much better than random much
比随机好多 了好多 了
better than 10%
优于10％
we can do 35 38 percent accuracy
我们可以做到38 ％的准确率
that's a classifier we have our first
这是我们的第一个分类器
classifier K nearest neighbors let's
分类器K最近的邻居 让我们
take our classifier to a whole new level
把我们的分类器提升到一个全新的水平
instead of comparing it to just fight
而不是将它比作战斗
trying to find one image that's the
试图找到一个图像
closest in our data set we tried to find
我们试图找到最接近我们的数据集
K closest and say what is what class do
K最接近并说出什么是上课
the majority of them belong to and we
他们中的大多数属于 我们
take that k and increase it for 1 to 2
取k并将其增加1到2
to 3 to 4 to 5 and see how that changes
到3到4到5 ，看看它是如何 变化的
the problem with seven years neighbors
七年 邻居 的问题
which is the optimal under this approach
这种方法下的最佳选择
for CFR 10 we achieve 30% accuracy
对于CFR 10，我们实现了 30％的 准确性
human level is 95% accuracy and with
人的水平为 95％ 的准确度，并 用
convolutional neural networks will get
卷积神经网络将得到
very close to 100% that's where you'll
非常接近100％，这就是你要去的地方
networks shine this very task of bending
网络照亮了 这个弯曲的任务
images it all starts at this basic
这一切都是从这个基础开始的
computational unit signal in each of the
每个计算单元信号
signals are weighed summed bias added
信号加权加总偏差
and put an input into a nonlinear
并把一个输入 到 非线性
activation function that produces an
激活功能， 产生一个
output the nonlinear activation function
输出非线性激活函数
is key all of these put together and
是所有这些放在一起的关键
more and more hidden layers form a deep
越来越多的隐藏层形成了深层次
neural network and that deep neural
神经网络和深层神经网络
network is trained as we've discussed by
正如我们所讨论的那样，对网络进行了培训
taking a forward pass and examples have
采取前进传球和例子
garage with labels seeing how close
车库与标签看到有多接近
those labels are to the real ground
那些标签是真实的
truth and then punishing the weights
真相然后惩罚权重
that resulted in the incorrect decisions
这导致了错误的决定
and rewarding the weights that resulted
并奖励所产生的重量
in correct decisions for the case of 10
正确决定 10 的情况
examples the output of the network is
示例 网络 的输出 是
different values the input being
输入的不同值
handwritten digits from 0 to 9 for 10 of
手写数字从0到9 为 10
those and we wanted our network to
那些我们希望我们的网络
classify what is in this image of a
分类 什么的这个形象
handwritten digit is it 1 is 0 1 2 3
手写的数字是1是0 1 2 3
through 9 the way it's often done is
到 9 它经常 做 的 方式 是
there's ten outputs of the network and
有十个 网络 输出 和
each of the neurons on the output is
输出中的每个神经元都是
responsible for getting really excited
负责得到 真正的兴奋
when it's number is called and everybody
当它的号码 被召唤时 ，每个人
else is supposed to be not excited
别的应该 不会兴奋
therefore the number of classes is the
因此 班级 的 数量 是
number of outputs that's how it's
输出数量就是这样的
commonly done and you assign a class to
通常完成，你分配一个类
the input image based on the highest the
输入图像基于最高的
neuron which produces the highest output
产生最高输出的神经元
but that's for a fully connected network
但这是一个完全连接的网络
that we've discussed on Monday there is
我们已经在周一讨论有
in deep learning a lot of tricks that
深入学习了许多技巧
make things work that make training much
使事情的工作 ，使培训成为 多
more efficient on large class problems
在大班问题上更有效率
where there's a lot of classes on large
那里有很多课程
data sets when the representation that
表示时的 数据 集
the neural network is tasked with
神经网络的任务是
learning is extremely complex and that's
学习是非常复杂的，那就是
where convolutional neural neural
卷积神经神经网络
networks step in the trick they use a
网络介入他们使用的技巧
spatial invariance they use the idea
空间不变性他们使用这个想法
that a cat in the top left corner of an
在的 左上角猫
image is the same as a cat in the bottom
图像与底部的猫相同
right corner of an image so we can learn
图像的右上角，这样我们就可以学习
the same features across the image
整个图像具有相同的功能
that's where the convolution operation
这就是卷积操作的地方
steps in instead of the fully connected
步骤而不是完全连接
networks here there's a third dimension
这里的网络有第三个 维度
of depth so the blocks in this neural
深度所以这个神经元中的块
network as input take 3d volumes and as
网络作为输入拍摄3D体积和
output produced 3d volumes
输出产生了3d卷
a slice of the image a window and slide
的图像的窗口和滑动件的切片
it across applying the same exact
它应用相同的精确
weights and we'll go through an example
权重， 我们将通过 一个 例子
the same exact weights as in the fully
与完全相同的确切权重
connected network on the edges that are
连接网络的边缘
used to map the input to the output here
用于 将输入 映射 到输出
are used to map this slice of an image
用于映射 图像的 这个切片
this window of an image to the output
这个窗口的图像输出
and you can make several many of such
你 可以做很多这样的 事情
convolutional filters many layers many
卷积过滤很多层
different options of what kind of
什么样的不同的选择
features you look for in an image
您在图像中寻找的功能
what kind of window you slide across in
你滑过什么样的窗户
order to extract all kinds of things all
为了提取各种各样的东西
kinds of edges all kind of higher-order
各种 边缘各种高阶
patterns in the images the very
图像中的图案非常
important thing is the parameters on
重要的是参数
each of these filters the subset of the
每个这些滤波器的 所述 子集
image these windows are shared if the
图像这些窗口是共享的， 如果
feature that defines a cat is useful in
定义猫的功能非常有用
the top left corner it's useful in the
它的左上角很有用
top right corner it's useful in every
在右上角它对每一个都很有用
aspect of the image this is the trick
图像方面这是诀窍
that makes convolutional neural networks
这使得卷积神经网络
save a lot of a lot of parameters reduce
节省了很多参数减少 了很多
parameter significantly it's the reuse
参数显着的重用
the spatial sharing of features across
跨越特征的空间共享
the space of the image the depth of
图像的空间深度
these 3d volumes is the number of
这些3d 卷的数量是
filters the stride is the skip of the
过滤步幅是跳过
filter the step size how many pixels you
过滤步长你有多少像素
skip when you apply the filter to the
将过滤器应用到的时跳过
input and the padding is
输入和填充是
they're padding the zero padding on the
他们填充 的 零填充
outside of the input to a convolutional
卷积之外的输入
layer let's go through an example so on
图层让我们来看一个例子
the left here and the slides are now
左边这里和幻灯片现在
available online you can follow them
在线提供，您 可以关注他们
along and I'll step through this example
沿着我将逐步通过 这个例子
on the left here is a input volume of
在左边 这里 是输入音量
three channels the left column is the
左列 是三个通道
input the three block the three squares
输入三个 块三个 方块
there are the three channels and there's
有三个渠道，有
numbers inside those channels and then
内的那些信道， 然后数
we have a filter in red two of them two
我们有一个红色的过滤器，其中两个是两个
channels of filters with a bias and we
具有偏差的滤波器通道和我们
those filters are three by three each
那些过滤器各有三个
one of them is size three by three and
其中一个是尺寸三乘三
what we do is we take those three by
我们做的是，我们通过采取这三个
three filters that are to be learned
要学习的三个过滤器
these are our variables our weights that
这些是我们的变量我们的权重
we have to learn and then we slide it
我们必须学习，然后我们滑动它
across an image to produce the output on
整个图像以产生所述 输出 上
the right the green so by applying the
右侧的绿色所以通过应用
filters in the red there's two of them
在红色过滤器中有两个
and within each one there's one for
每一个都有 一个
every input channel we go from the left
每个输入通道我们从左边开始
to the right from the input volume on
从输入音量开到右边
the left to the output volume green on
左边的输出音量为 绿色
the right and you can look it you can
右边你可以看看它
pull up the slides yourself now if you
如果你现在自己拉起幻灯片
can't see the numbers on the screen but
看不到屏幕上的数字 但是
the the operations are performed on the
操作是在。上执行的
input to produce the single value that's
输入产生单值的
highlighted there in the green and the
突出显示在绿色 和
output and we slide this convolution no
输出， 我们滑动这个卷积没有
filter along the image with a stride in
沿着图像过滤， 大步进入
this case of to skipping skipping along
这种跳过跳过的情况
they sum to the to the right the two
他们总结到 了右边 的两个
channel output in green that's it
绿色的通道输出就是它
the convolutional operation that's
卷积操作这
what's called the convolutional layer
什么叫卷积层
neural networks and the parameters here
神经网络和这里的参数
besides the bias are the read values in
除了偏差是 读取值
the middle that's what we're trying to
中间就是我们想要的
learn and there's a lot of interesting
学习，有很多有趣的东西
tricks we'll discuss today on top of
招数我们今天要讨论的顶部
those but this is at the core this is
那些，但这是核心
the spatially invariant sharing of
空间不变的共享
parameters that make convolutional
卷积的参数
neural networks able to efficiently
神经网络能够 有效地进行
learn and find patterns and images to
学习和找到模式和图像
build your intuition a little bit more
更多地建立你的直觉
about convolution here's an input image
关于卷积这里是一个输入图像
on the left and on the right the
在左边和右边
identity filter produces the output you
身份过滤器产生你的输出
see on the right and then there's
看到右边然后有
different ways you can different kinds
不同的方式你 可以不同的种类
of edges you can extract with the
你可以 提取的边缘
activate or the resulting activation map
激活或生成的激活 映射
seen on the right so when applying the
在右边看到所以申请时
filters with those edge detection
带有边缘检测的滤波器
filters to the image on the left you
过滤到你左边的图像
produce in white are the parts that
以白色生产的是 那些部件
activate the convolution the results of
激活卷积的结果
these filters and so you can do any kind
这些过滤器，所以你可以做任何种类
of filter that's what we're trying to
过滤器就是我们想要的
learn any kind of edge any kind of any
学习任何一种边缘
kind of pattern you can move along in
你可以移动的那种模式
this window and this way that's shown
这个窗口以及显示的方式
here you slide along the image and you
在这里你沿着 图像和你 滑动
produce the output you see on the right
产生你在右边看到的输出
and depending on how many filters you
并取决于你有多少过滤器
have in every level you have many of
在每个级别 你都有很多
such slices VC on the right the input on
这样的切片VC就在右侧输入上
the left the output on the right if you
左边的输出 如果你的话
have dozens of filters you have dozens
有几十个过滤器，你有几十个
of images on the right each with
每个用右边的图像
different results that show where each
不同的结果 显示每个
of the individual filter patterns were
个别过滤器模式是
found and we learned what patterns are
发现并且我们学会了什么样的模式
useful to look for in order to perform
有用的寻找， 以便 执行
the classification task that's the task
作为任务的分类任务
for the neural network to learn these
为神经网络学习这些
filters
过滤器
and the filters have higher and higher
并且过滤器越来越高
order of representation going from the
表示的顺序从去
very basic edges to the high semantics
高语义的非常基本的边缘
meaning that spans entire images and the
意味着跨越整个图像和
ability to spend images can be done in
花费图像的能力可以在
several ways but traditionally has been
传统上有 几种 方式
successfully done through max pooling
通过max pooling成功完成
through pooling of taking the output of
通过统一取得产出
convolutional operation and reducing the
卷积操作和减少
resolution of that byte by condensing
通过压缩来解析该 字节
that information by for example taking
该信息通过例如采取
the maximum values the maximum
最大值最大值
activations therefore reducing the
激活因此减少了
spatial resolution which has detrimental
它 有利于空间分辨率
effects as we'll talk about in the scene
我们将 在场景中 讨论的效果
segmentation but it's beneficial for
细分，但它有益于
finding higher order representations and
找到更高阶的表示和
the images that bring images together
将图像组合在一起的图像
that bring features together to form an
将功能结合在一起形成一个
entity that we're trying to identify and
我们试图识别的 实体
classify okay so that forms a
分类好，以便形成一个
convolution Yool network such
卷积Yool网络这样的
convolutional layers stacked on top of
卷积层叠在上面
each other is the only addition to a
彼此是唯一的补充
neural network that makes for a
神经网络， 使一
convolutional neural network and then at
卷积神经网络然后在
the end the fully connected layers or
结束完全连接的层或
any kind of other architectures allow us
任何其他架构都允许 我们
to apply particular domains
应用特定域名
let's take image net as a case study an
让我们像网作为案例研究 的
image net the data set an image net the
图像网络数据集图像网络
challenge
挑战
the task is classification as I
任务是我的分类
mentioned the first lecture image net is
提到第一个图像网是
a data set one of the largest in the
数据集中最大的 一个
world of images with 14 million images
图像 的世界有14万张图片
21,000 categories and a lot of depth to
21000个类别和很多深度 ，以
many of the categories as I mentioned
我提到的很多类别
1200 granny smith apples
1200奶奶史密斯苹果
these allow - these allow the newer
这些允许- 这些允许更新
networks to learn the rich
网络学习富人
representations in both pose lighting
姿势照明中的表示
variability and intraclass class
变异性和类内类
variation for the particular things
特定事物的变化
particular classes like granny smith
像格兰尼史密斯这样的特殊课程
apples so let's look through the various
苹果让我们期待通过各种
networks let's discuss them let's see
网络让我们讨论它们让我们看看
the insights
见解
it started with Alex net the first
它始于Alex网络的第一个
really big successful GPU trained neural
真正成功的GPU 训练神经
network on image net that's achieved a
在图像网上实现了一个网络
significant boost over the previous year
比去年大幅提升
and moved on to vgg net Google net ague
并转移到 VGG净净谷歌 疟疾
Lynnette ResNet see you image and as
Lynnette RESNET 看到你的图像和
Annette in 2017 again the numbers will
安妮特在2017年 的数字将 再次 出现
show for the accuracy are based on the
显示的准确性是基于
top five error rate we get five guesses
前五个错误率我们得到五个 猜测
and it's a one or zero if you get guess
如果你猜到它就是一个或零
if one of the five is correct you get a
如果五个中的一个 是正确的，你得到一个
one for that particular guess otherwise
否则 就是一个特别的 猜测
it's a zero and human error is five
它是零，人为错误是五
point one when a human tries to achieve
当人类试图实现时，指出一点
the same tries to perform the same task
同样尝试执行相同的任务
as the machinist task of doing the air
作为机械师的空气任务
is five point one the human annotation
是人类注释的五点一点
is performed on the images based on
基于的图像执行
binary classification Granny Smith apple
二元分类格兰尼 史密斯苹果
or not cat or not the actual tasks that
或不是猫或不是实际的 任务
the machine has to perform and that the
机器必须执行和 那个
human competing has to perform is given
人类的竞争必须执行给定
an image is provide one of the many
图像提供 众多之一
classes under that human errors 5.1%
人为错误下的课程5.1％
which was surpassed in 2015 by ResNet to
将其在2015年超过由RESNET 到
achieve four percent error so let's
实现4％的误差，让我们来吧
with Alex net I'll zoom in on the later
与Alex网格我将放大 后期
networks they have some interesting
他们有一些有趣的网络
insights but Alex net and vgg net both
见解， 但 亚历克斯网和vgg网两个
fall at a very similar architecture very
落在一个非常类似的架构非常
uniform throughout its depth vgg net in
整个深度均匀的vgg网
2014 is convolution convolution pooling
2014年是卷积卷积池
convolution pooling convolution pooling
卷积池卷积池
and fully connected layers at the end
并在最后完全连接层
there's a certain kind of beautiful
有一种美丽
simplicity uniformity to these
这些简单均匀
architectures because you can just make
架构因为你可以做到
it deeper and deeper and makes it very
它越来越 深，使它变得非常
amenable to implementation in a layer
适合在图层中实现
stack kind of way and in any of the deep
堆栈的方式和任何深刻的
learning frameworks it's clean and
学习框架很干净
beautiful to understand in the case of
美丽 在这种情况下 要理解
eg gina was 16 or 19 layers with 138
例如，吉娜 是16 或19层，138
million parameters not many
百万参数不多
optimizations and these parameters
优化和这些参数
therefore the number of parameters is
因此 参数的数量 是
much higher than the networks that
远高于网络
followed it despite the layers not being
尽管没有层次，但它紧随其后
that large Google Net introduced the
大型谷歌网推出了
inception module starting to do some
初始模块开始做一些
interesting things with the small
有趣的事情与 小
modules within these networks which
这些网络中的模块
allow for the training to be more
允许培训更多
efficient and effective the idea behind
高效而有效的理念背后
the inception module shown here with the
此处显示的初始模块包含
previous layer on bottom and the
前一层在底部和
convolutional layer here with the
卷积层在这里用
inception module on top produced on top
在顶部生成的初始模块
is it used the idea that different size
它是否使用了不同 大小 的想法
convolutions provide different value for
卷积为...提供不同的价值
the network smaller convolutions are
网络 较小的卷积是
able to capture or propagate forward
能够捕获 或传播前进
features that are very local a high
特点是 非常局部的 高
resolution in in in texture larger
纹理中的分辨率更大
convolutions are better able to
卷积更好
represent and capture and catch highly
代表并捕获并高度捕捉
abstracted features higher-order
抽象的功能更高阶
features so the idea behind the
功能所以背后的想法
inception module is to say well as
初始模块就是说得好
opposed to choosing and high in a high
反对选择和高位
pair
对
tuning process or architecture design
调整过程 或架构设计
process choosing which convolution size
过程选择哪个卷积大小
we want to go with why not do all of
我们要 一起去 ，为什么不能做所有的
them together while several together in
他们在一起 ，而几个一起
the case of the Google net model there's
谷歌网模型就是这样的
the one by one three by three and five
一个接一个三乘三， 五
by five convolutions with the old trusty
与旧信托五次合并
friend of max pooling still left in
max pooling的朋友还留在了
there as well which has lost favor more
在那里已经失去了 更多的 青睐
and more over time for the image
随着时间的推移 ， 更多 的图像
classification task and the results is
分类 任务和结果是
there's fewer parameters are required if
如果 需要 的 参数 更少
you pick the placing of these inception
你选择这些开始的位置
modules correctly the number of
模块正确的数量
parameters required to achieve a higher
要求 达到更高的参数
performance is much lower res net one of
性能远低于res net one
the most popular still to date
迄今为止最受欢迎的
architectures that we'll discuss in
架构，我们将讨论
scene segmentation as well came up and
现场分割也出现 了
use the idea of a residual block the
使用残余块的想法
initial inspiring observation which
最初鼓舞人心的观察
doesn't necessarily hold true as it
并不一定适用于它
turns out but that network depth
结果却是 网络深度
increases representation power so these
增加表现力这些
residual blocks allow you to have much
残余块允许你有很多
deeper networks and I'll explain why in
更深层的网络，我将解释为什么在
a second here but the thought was they
这里的第二个， 但他们的想法是
work so well because the network's so
工作得那么 好，因为网络是如此
much deeper the key thing that makes
更深层次， 使关键的事情
these blocks so effective is the same
这些块如此有效是一样的
idea that's that reminiscent of
这让人联想到的想法
recurrent neural networks that I hope
我希望 复发神经 网络
would get a chance to talk about the
我们 有机会谈论 这个问题
training of them is much easier they
他们的训练要容易得多
take a simple block repeated over and
采取一个简单的块重复和
over and they pass the input along
结束，他们 传递输入
without transformation along with the
没有转变与
ability to transform it to learn to
转化它 以学习的能力
learn the filters learn the weights
学习过滤器学习权重
so you're allowed to you're allow every
所以你被允许每个人都允许
layer to not only take on the processing
图层不仅要承担处理
of previous layers but to take in the
以前的图层， 但要接受
wrong transform data and learn something
错误的 转换数据和学习的东西
new the ability to learn something new
学习新东西的新能力
allows you to have much deeper networks
允许您拥有更深入的网络
and the simplicity of this block allows
并且这个块的简单性允许
for more effective training the state of
为了更有效的培训状态
the art in 2017 the winner is squeezed
2017年的艺术作品 受到挤压
and excitation networks that unlike the
激发网络， 不像
previous year will see you image which
前一年会看到你的形象
simply took ensemble methods and
简单地采用整体方法和
combined a lot of successful approaches
结合了许多 成功的方法
to take a marginal improvement se net
采取边际改善自身净
got a significant improvement at least
至少得到了显着的改善
in percentages I think there's a 25%
百分比我认为有 25％
reduction in error from 4 percent to 3
误差从4％减少到3
percent something like that by using a
百分之东西 那样 使用
very simple idea that I think is
很简单的想法 ，我认为 是
important to mention a simple insight
重要的是提 一个简单的见解
it added a parameter to each channel and
它为每个 频道添加了一个参数
the convolutional layer in the
卷积层
convolutional block so the network can
卷积块所以网络可以
now adjust the weighting on each channel
现在调整每个频道的权重
based for for each feature map based on
基于的每个特征图的基础
the content based on the input to the
根据 输入的 内容
network this is kind of a take away to
网络这是一种 带走的东西
think about about any of the networks
想想任何一个网络
who talk about any of the architectures
谁 谈论任何架构
is a lot of times your recurrent neural
很多时候你的反复神经
networks and convolutional neural
网络和卷积神经网络
networks have tricks that significantly
网络有很大的技巧
reduce the number of parameters the bulk
减少批量 参数 的数量
the sort of low-hanging fruit they use
他们使用的那种低悬的水果
spatial invariants a temporal invariants
空间不变量是时间 不变量
to reduce the number of parameters to
减少参数的数量
represent the input data but they also
代表输入数据 但它们也是
leave certain things not parameterize
留下某些不参数化的东西
they don't allow the network to learn it
他们不允许网络学习它
allow in this case the network to learn
在这种情况下允许网络学习
the weighting on each of the individual
对每个人的加权
channels so each of the individual
通道，因此每个 单独的
filters is something that you learn as
过滤器是你学到的东西
along with the filters takes it makes a
与过滤器一起使用它
huge boost
巨大的提振
the cool thing about this is it's
关于这个很酷的事情就是它
applicable to any architecture this kind
适用于任何 这种 架构
of block that's kind of what the the
块的那 是什么的
squeeze and excitation block is
挤压和激励块是
applicable to any architecture and
适用于任何架构和
because obviously it it just simply
因为很明显它 只是简单地
permit Rises the ability to choose which
permit 提高选择哪个的能力
filter you go with based on the content
过滤你去与基于内容
it's a subtle but crucial thing I think
我认为 这是一个微妙但至关重要的事情
it's pretty cool and for future research
它非常酷，适合未来的研究
it inspires to think about what else can
它激发了思考还能做些什么
be parameterize in your own networks
在您自己的网络中进行参数化
what else can be controlled as part of
还有什么可以被控制 的 一部分
the learning process including hiring
学习过程包括招聘
higher-order hyper parameters which
高阶超参数
which aspects of the training and the
培训的哪些方面和
architecture of the network can be part
网络的架构可以是一部分
of the learning this is what this
学习的 ，这是这是什么
network inspires another network has
网络启发了另一个网络
been in development since the 90s ideas
自90年代以来 一直处于发展阶段
with geoff hinton but really received
与杰夫辛顿，但真的收到了
has been published on received
已发表收到
significant attention 2017 that i won't
重点关注2017年我不会
go into detail here we are going to
进入这里的细节 ， 我们将
release an online-only
在线发布
video about capsule networks it's a
关于胶囊网络的视频是一个
little bit too technical but they
有点太技术 但 他们
inspire a very important point that we
激励很重要的一点 ， 我们
should always think about with deep
应该总是深思熟虑
learning whenever it's successful is to
学习什么时候才能成功
think about what as I mentioned with the
考虑一下我提到的内容
cat eating a banana on a philosophical
猫 在哲学上吃香蕉
and the mathematical level you have to
和 你必须 的数学 水平
consider what assumptions these networks
考虑这些网络的假设
make and what through those assumptions
通过这些假设做出什么
they throw away so neural networks due
他们扔掉由于这样的神经网络
to the spatial with convolutional neural
卷积神经网络的空间
networks due to their spatial invariants
网络由于 其空间 不变量
throw away information about the
扔掉 有关信息
relationship between the the hierarchies
层次结构 之间 的关系
between the simple and the complex
简单和 复杂之间
objects so the face on the left and the
对象所以面对左边和
face on the right looks the same to
右边的脸看起来 一样
accomplish a neural network the presence
完成神经网络的存在
of eyes and nose and mouth is the
眼睛和鼻子和嘴巴是
central aspect of what makes
是什么使得中心方面
classification tasks work for
分类任务适用于
convolution Network where it will fire
卷积网络 将在哪里发射
and say this is definitely a face but
并说这绝对是一张脸但是
the spatial relationship is lost is
丢失的空间关系
ignored
忽视
which means there's a lot of
这意味着有很多
implications to this but for things like
对此的影响，但对于像这样的事情
pose variation that information is lost
摆脱信息丢失的变异
we're throwing away that away completely
我们 完全 扔掉 了
and hoping that the pooling operation
并希望 汇集操作
that's performing these networks is able
正在执行这些网络是有能力的
to sort of mesh everything together to
把所有东西都整合在一起
come up with the features that are
想出了 这些功能
firing of the different parts of the
射击 的不同部分
face that then come up with the total
面对 再拿出 总
classification that it's a face without
这是一个没有脸的分类
representing really the relationship
代表真正的关系
between these features at the low level
在低级别的这些功能之间
and and the high level at the low level
和低水平的高水平
of the hierarchy at the simple and the
简单和等级的层次结构
complex level this is a super exciting
复杂程度这 是一个超级刺激的
field now that's hopefully will spark
现在这个领域有希望激发
developments of how we design your own
我们如何设计自己的发展
networks that are able to learn this the
能够 学习这个 的网络
rotational the orientation invariance as
旋转方向不变性为
well ok so as I mentioned you take these
好吧，所以我 提到你拿这些
combos in your networks chop off the
你网络中的组合 切断了
final layer in order to apply to a
最后一层，以申请一个
particular domain and that is what we'll
特定领域，这 就是我们所要做的
do with fully convolutional neural
做完全卷积神经
networks the ones that we task to
网络我们的任务
segment the image at a pixel level as a
将像素级别的图像分割 为
reminder these networks through the
提醒这些网络 通过
convolutional process are really
卷积过程确实如此
producing a heat map different parts of
产生热图的 不同部分
the network are getting excited based on
网络越来越兴奋了
the different aspects of the image and
图像的不同方面和
so it can be used to do the localization
所以它可以用来进行本地化
of detecting not just classifying the
检测不仅仅是分类
image but localizing the object and they
图像，但本地化对象和他们
could do so at a pixel level so the
可以在像素级别这样做
convolutional layers are doing the
卷积层正在做
encoding process they're taking the rich
编码过程他们带走了富人
raw sensory information in the image and
图像和图像中的原始感官信息
encoding them into an interpretable set
将它们编码为可解释的集合
of features representation that can then
然后可以表示特征表示
be used for classification but we can
可用于 分类 ，但我们可以
also then use it
然后使用它
kotor up sample that information and
kotor up样本信息和
produce a map like this fully
完全生成这样的地图
convolutional neural network
卷积神经网络
segmentation semantic scene segmentation
分割语义 场景分割
image segmentation the goal is to as
图像分割的 目标是
opposed to classify the entire image you
相对于整个图像要划分
classify every single pixel its pixel
将每个像素分类为其像素
level segmentation you color every
每个颜色的水平分割
single pixel with what that pixel what
单个像素与那个像素是什么
object that pixel belongs to in this 2d
像素属于这个2d的对象
space of the image the 2d projection the
2d投影的图像空间
in the image of a 3-dimensional world so
在三维世界的形象中如此
the thing is there's been a lot of
事情是有很多
advancement in the last three years but
过去 三年的进步但是
it's still an incredibly difficult
它仍然非常困难
problem if you if you think if you think
问题，如果你认为 如果 你 认为
about the amount of data that's used for
- 这就是 使用 的数据量
training and the task of pixel level of
训练和像素级别的任务
megapixels here of millions of pixels
百万像素这里有数百万 像素
that are tasked with having a scientist
负责有科学家的任务
single label it's an extremely difficult
单一标签这是一个非常困难的
problem why is this interesting
问题为什么这 很有趣
important problem to try to solve as
试图解决的重要问题
opposed to bounding boxes around cats
反对围绕猫的边界框
well it's whenever precise boundaries of
好吧，只要精确的边界
objects are important certainly medical
对象很重要， 当然是医学
applications when looking at imaging and
看待成像和应用时的应用
detecting in particular for example
特别是例如检测
detecting tumors in the in in medical
检测医学中的肿瘤
imaging of different different organs
不同器官的成像
and in driving in robotics when objects
当物体在机器人中驾驶时
are involved it's a done scene of all
参与它是一个完成所有的场景
those vehicles pedestrians cyclists we
那些车辆行人骑自行车的我们
need to be able to not just have a loose
需要能够不只是 松散
estimate of where objects are we need to
估计我们需要的对象
be able to have the exact boundaries and
能够拥有确切的界限和
then potentially through data fusion
然后可能通过数据融合
fusing sensors together
将传感器融合在一起
fusing this rich textural information
融合这些丰富的纹理信息
about pedestrians cyclists and vehicles
关于行人骑自行车者和车辆
to lidar data that's providing us the
为我们提供的 激光雷达数据
three-dimensional map of the world or
世界的三维地图或
have both the semantic meaning of the
同时具有语义的意义
different objects and their exact
不同的对象和他们的确切
three-dimensional location
三维位置
a lot of this work successfully a lot of
很多这项 工作 的 成功 有很多
the work in the semantic segmentation
语义分割中的工作
started with fully convolutional
从完全卷积开始
networks for semantic segmentation paper
用于语义分割的网络
FCN that's where the name of FCN came
FCN就是FCN的名字来源
from in november 2014
从2014年11月起
now go through a few papers here to give
现在通过这里的几篇论文给出
you some intuition where the field is
你是一个直觉领域
gone and how that takes us to seg fuse
走了，这又怎么会让我们陷入困境
the segmentation competition so FCM
FCM的细分竞争
repurposed the image net pre-trained
重新利用预先训练过的图像网
nets the nets that were trained to
捕获 训练过的网
classify what's in an image the entire
分类整个图像中的内容
image and chopped off the fully
图像并完全切断
connected layers and then added decoder
连接层然后添加解码器
parts that that up sample there the
在那里采样的零件
image to produce a heat map here shown
此处显示的图像生成热图
with a tabby cat a heat map of where the
与大花猫的其中一个热图
cat is in the image it's a much slower
猫在 图像中它慢得多
much coarser resolution than the input
比输入更粗糙的分辨率
image 1/8 at best
图片1/8充其量
skip connections to improve coarseness
跳过连接以改善粗糙度
of up sampling there's a few tricks if
如果， 采样有一些 技巧
you do the most naive approach the up
你做的最 幼稚的做法 向上
sampling is going to be extremely coarse
抽样将非常粗糙
because that's the whole point of the
因为那是整个问题
neural network the encoding part is you
神经网络 编码部分就是你
throw away all the useless data the
抛弃所有 无用的数据
YouTube the most essential aspects that
YouTube上最重要的方面 是
represent that image so you're throwing
代表那个图像让你投掷
away a lot of information that's
远离了很多信息
necessary to then form a high resolution
然后必须形成高分辨率
image so there's a few tricks where you
图像 所以你有一些技巧
skip a few of the final pooling
跳过一些最后的汇集
operations to go in similar way and this
操作进去类似的方式，这
is a residual block to go to go to the
是残差块去 去
output produce higher and higher
产出越来越高
resolution heat map at the end segment
结束段的分辨率热图
in 2015 applied this to the driving
在2015年将此应用于驾驶
context and really taking it to kitty
背景和真正把它带到小猫
data set and have have shown a lot of
数据集和已经都表现出了很大 的
interesting results and really explored
有趣的结果，并真正探索
the encoder decoder or formulation of
编码器解码器或配方
the problem
问题
really solidifying this the place of the
真正巩固了这个地方
encoder/decoder framework for the
编码器/解码器框架
segmentation task dilated convolution
分割任务扩张卷积
I'm taking you through a few components
我带你了解一些组件
which are critical here to the state of
这对于国家来说至关重要
the art dilated convolutions so the
本 领域扩张卷积所以
convolution operation as the pooling
卷积操作作为汇集
operation reduces resolution
操作会降低分辨率
significantly and dilated convolution
显着和扩张的卷积
has a certain kind of gritting as
有一定的 gritting作为
visualized there that maintains the
在那里可视化维护着
local high resolution textures while
局部高分辨率纹理而
still capturing the spatial window
还是捕捉 空间窗
necessary
必要
it's called dilated convolutional layer
它被称为扩张卷积层
and that's in a 2015 paper proved to be
这证明是2015年的一篇论文
much better at up sampling a high
在上 采样 高好得多
resolution image deep lab with a be v1
分辨率图像深度实验室与v1
v2 Navi 3 added conditional random
v2 Navi 3添加了条件随机
fields which is the final piece of the
这是最后一块的
of the state-of-the-art puzzle here a
这里 有 最先进的 谜题
lot of the successful networks today
今天很多成功的网络
that do segmentation not all do post
做分段不是所有发布的
process using CRFs conditional random
使用CRF的过程有条件随机
fields and what they do is they smooth
田野和他们所做的是他们顺利
the segmentation the up sample
分割向上 样品
segmentation that results from the FCN
由FCN产生的细分
by looking at the underlying image
通过查看底层图像
intensities so that's the key aspects of
强度，这是关键方面
the successful approaches today you have
你今天成功的方法
the encoder decoder framework of a fully
编码器解码器框架完全
accomplished in your network it replaces
在您的网络中完成它取代
the fully connected layers with the
完全连接的层与
convolutional layers deconvolution
卷积层反卷积
layers and as the years progress from
层和随着时间的进展 ，从
2014 to today as usual than underlying
2014 年至今为常，而不是潜在的
networks from alex net to vgg net and to
从alex net到 vgg net的网络
now ResNet have been one of the big
现在ResNet已经成为其中之一
reasons for the improvements of these
这些改进的原因
to be able to perform the segmentation
能够执行分割
so naturally they mirrored the imagenet
所以他们很自然地反映了 imagenet
challenge performance in adapting these
挑战性能以 适应这些
networks so the state-of-the-art uses
网络因此是最先进的 用途
ResNet or similar networks conditional
ResNet或类似网络 有条件
random fields for smoothing based on the
用于平滑的随机字段
input image intensities and the dilated
输入图像强度和扩张
convolution that maintains the
卷积维持着
computational cost but increases the
计算成本但增加了
resolution of the up sampling throughout
整个上采样的分辨率
the intermediate feature Maps and that
中间特征地图和那
takes us to the state of the art that we
把我们带到了技术状态， 我们
used to produce the images to produce
用于产生图像 以产生
the images for the competition present
比赛的图像存在
that do you see for dance up sampling
你看到 舞蹈采样 了吗？
convolution instead of bilinear up
卷积而不是双线性
sampling you make the up sampling learn
抽样你做上采样学习
about you learn the upscaling filters
关于你学习升级过滤器
that's on the bottom that's really the
这是真正的底部
key part that made it work there should
使它在那里工作的关键部分应该
be a theme here sometimes the the
是一个主题在这里 有时在
biggest addition they can be done this
最大的补充他们可以做到这一点
parameter izing one of the aspects of
参数化的一个方面
the network they've taken for granted
他们认为理所当然的网络
letting the network learn that aspect
让网络了解这方面
and the other I'm not sure how important
而另一个 我 不确定有多重要
it is to the success but it's a it's a
这是成功， 但它是一个
cool little addition is a hybrid dilated
酷少添加是混合扩张
convolution as I showed that
正如我所表明的那样卷积
visualization where the convolution is
卷积的可视化
spread apart a little bit in the input
在输入中分散一点点
from the input to the output the steps
从输入到输出的步骤
of that dilated convolution filter when
那个扩张的卷积滤波器的时候
they're changed it produces a smoother
他们改变了它会更顺畅
result because when it's kept the same
结果，因为它保持 不变
there certain input pixels get a lot
某些输入像素获得了很多
more attention than others so losing
更多的关注比其他人如此 失去
that favoritism is what's achieved by
偏袒是所取得的成就
using a variable different dilation rate
使用可变的不同膨胀率
those are the two tricks but really the
这些是两个技巧，但真的是
biggest one is the parameterization of
最大的一个是 参数化
the upscaling filters okay so that's
向上变换过滤好 了，这就是
what we're that's what we used to
我们这就是我们以前的样子
generate that data and that's what we
生成那些数据，那就是我们
provides you the code with if you're
如果你有的话， 为 你 提供 代码
interested in competing in psyche views
有兴趣参加精神观
the other aspect here that everything
这里的另一个方面是一切
we've talked about from the
我们已经谈过 了
classification to the segmentation to
分类到分割 ，以
making sense of images is it there the
理解图像是有的
information about time the temporal
有关时间 的 信息
dynamics of the scene is thrown away and
现场的动态被扔掉
for the driving context of the robotics
为了机器人的驾驶环境
contest and what we'd like to do with
比赛 和我们想 和做 什么
psyche fuse for the segmentation
用于分割的灵魂融合
dynamics scene segmentation context of
动态场景分割上下文
when you try to interpret what's going
当你试图解释发生了什么
on in the scene over time and use that
随着时间的推移在场景中使用它
information time is essential thus the
因此，信息时间至关重要
movement of pixels is essential through
像素的运动是必不可少的，通过
time that that understanding how those
那时候那个了解 那些
objects move in a 3d space through the
物体通过三维空间移动
2d projection of an image it's
它的2d投影图像
fascinating and us there's a lot of set
令人着迷，我们有很多 设置
of open problems there so flow is what's
那些开放性问题 所以流动是什么
very helpful to as a starting point to
作为一个起点非常有帮助
help us understand how these pixels move
帮助我们了解这些像素如何移动
flow optical flow dense optical flow is
流动光流密集光流是
the computation that our best of a best
我们最好的计算
approximation of where each pixel in
近似每个像素的位置
image one and moved in the in
图像一并移入
temporarily following image after that
之后暂时下面的图片
there's two images in 30 frames a second
每秒30帧中有两个图像
there's one image at time zero the other
有一个图像时间为零 另一个
is 33.3 milliseconds later and the
是33.3毫秒 后和
idents optical flow is our best estimate
idents光流是我们最好的估计
of how each pixel in the input image
如何输入图像中的每个像素
moved to in the output image the optical
移动到输出图像中的光学
flow for every pixel produces a
每个像素的流量产生一个
direction of where we think that pixel
我们认为像素的方向
moved and the magnitude of how far moved
移动和移动的距离大小
that allows us to take information that
这使我们能够获取信息
we detected about the first frame and
我们检测到第一帧和
try to propagate it forward this is the
尝试传播转发这是
competition it's to try to segment an
竞争 是试图分割 一个
image and propagate that information
图像并传播该信息
forward for manual annotation of a
转发手动注释a
image so this kind of coloring book
图像所以这种着色书
annotation where you color every single
每个单独着色的注释
pixel in the state-of-the-art dataset
最先进的 数据集中的 像素
for driving cityscapes that it takes 1.5
用于驾驶城市景观需要1.5
ninth and 1.5 hours 90 minutes to do
第九和1.5小时 90分钟
that coloring that's 90 minutes per
每个90分钟的着色
image that's extremely long time that's
图像这是非常长的时间 这
why there doesn't exist today dataset
为什么今天不存在 数据集
and in this class we're going to create
在这堂课中我们要 创作
one of segmentation of these images
这些图像 的分割 之一
through time through video so long
透过时间通过视频这么久
videos where every single frame is fully
每个帧都完整的视频
segmented that's still an open problem
分段，这仍然是一个开放的问题
that we need to solve flows a piece of
我们需要解决流量问题
that and we also provide you the this
我们也为您提供此服务
computer state-of-the-art flow using
计算机最先进的流程使用
flow net 2.0 so flow net 1.0 in May 2015
流量净值2.0因此流量净值在2015年5月
used neural networks to learn the
用神经网络来学习
optical flow the dense optical flow and
光流密集的光流和
it did so with two kinds of
它2种这样做
architectures flow net s flowing that
建筑流动网络 流动
simple and flow net core flow net see
简单流网核流网见
the simple one is simply taking the two
简单的就是拿两个
images so what's what's the task here
图像所以 这里的任务 是什么
there's two images and you you want to
有两个图像，你想要的
produce from those two images they
从这两个图像中产生它们
follow each other in time thirty-three
三十三岁的时候跟着对方
point three milliseconds apart and your
点三毫秒和你的
task is the output to produce the dense
任务是产生密集的输出
optical flow so for the simple
光流如此简单
architecture you just stack them
架构你只是堆叠它们
together each are RGB so it produces a
每个 都是RGB，所以它产生一个
six channel input to the network there's
有六个通道输入网络
a lot of convolution and finally it's
很多卷积，最后是它
the the same kind of process as the
在同种工艺的的
fully convolution your networks to
将您的网络完全卷积到
produce the optical flow then there is
然后产生光流
flow net correlation architecture where
流网相关结构在哪里
you perform some convolution separately
你分别进行 一些卷积
before using a correlation layer to
在使用相关 层 之前
combine the feature Maps both
结合功能地图
effective in different data sets and
在不同的数据集和
different applications so flow net 2.0
不同的应用程序 所以流网2.0
in December 2016 is one of the
2016年12月是其中之一
state-of-the-art frameworks code bases
最先进的框架代码库
that we used to generate the data all
我们用来生成的所有数据
show combines the flow net Assam flow
show结合了流网阿萨姆流
net C and improves over the initial flow
净C并改善初始 流量
net producing a smoother flow field
净产生更平滑的流场
preserves the fine motion detail along
保留精细运动细节
the edges of the objects and it runs
对象的边缘并运行
extremely efficiently depending on the
非常有效地取决于
architecture there's a few variants
架构有一些变种
either eight to a hundred forty frames a
八到一百四十 帧a
second and the process there is
第二个和那个过程
essentially one that's common across
基本上是一个共同的
various applications deep learning is
各种应用 深度学习是
stacking these networks together the
将这些网络堆叠在一起
very interesting aspect here that we're
我们这里非常有趣的方面
still exploring and again applicable in
仍在探索并再次适用于
all of deep learning in this case it
在这种情况下所有深入学习它
seemed that there was a strong effect in
似乎有一个强有力的作用
taking sparse small multiple data set
采用稀疏的小多数据集
and doing the training the order of
并按顺序进行训练
which those data sets were used for the
它被用于组的那些数据
training process mattered a lot that's
训练过程中非常看重 这
very interesting
很有意思
so using flow net 2.0 here's the data
所以使用flow net 2.0这里是数据
set we're making available for psych
设置我们正在做供精极度紧张
fuse the competition cars that mit.edu
融合竞争的汽车，mit.edu
slash psych fuse first the original
斜线精神融合首先是原始的
video us driving in high-definition
视频我们以高清晰度驾驶
1080p and a 8k 360 video original video
1080p 和8k 360视频原始视频
driving around Cambridge
在剑桥附近开车
we're providing the ground truth for a
我们为一个人提供了基本的事实
training set for that training set for
训练集为该训练集
every single frame 30 frames a second
每个单帧 30帧的第二
we're providing the segmentation frame
我们正在提供细分框架
to frame to frame segmented on
框架到框架分段
Mechanical Turk we're also providing the
机械土耳其人我们也提供
output of the network that I mentioned
我提到 的网络输出
the state of their our segmentation
他们对我们的分割状态
network that's pretty damn close to the
那个非常接近的 网络
ground truth but still not and our task
事实但仍然没有 和我们的任务
is this is the interesting thing is our
这是有趣的事情是 我们的
task is to take the output of this
任务是把 这个 输出
network well there's two options one is
网络很好，有两种选择
to take the output of this network and
获取 此网络 的 输出 和
use use other networks to help you
使用其他网络来帮助你
propagate the information better so what
更好地传播信息
this segmentation the output of this
此分割 的 这个 输出
network does is it only takes a frame by
网络确实只需要一个帧
frame by frame it's not using the
逐帧， 它没有使用
temporal information at all so the
时间信息都是如此
question is can we figure out a way can
问题是我们可以找出一种方法可以
we figure out tricks to use temporal
我们想出使用时间的技巧
information to improve this segmentation
用于改善此细分的信息
so it looks more like this segmentation
所以看起来更像 是这种细分
and we're also
我们也是
providing the optical flow from frame to
提供从帧到光的光流
frame to frame so the optical flow based
帧到帧所以基于光流
on flowing at 2.00 of how each of the
在每个人的 2.00流动
pixels moved okay and that forms a seg
像素移动好 ，形成 一个 seg
fuse competition 10,000 images and the
融合竞争10000图像和
task is to submit code we have starter
任务是提交我们有启动的代码
code in Python and on github to take in
Python中的代码和github上的代码
the original video take in for the
原始视频接收
training set the ground truth the
训练奠定了基础的真相
segmentation from the state-of-the-art
从最先进的分割
segmentation Network the optical flow
分割网络 光流
from the state-of-the-art optical flow
来自最先进的光流
Network and taking that together to
网络 并将其 结合在一起
improve the the stuff on the bottom left
提高左下角的东西
the segmentation to try to achieve the
试图实现的细分
ground truth and on the top right okay
基本事实， 右上角没关系
with that I'd like to thank you tomorrow
我 明天 要 感谢你
at 1 p.m. is way mo in Stata 32 one two
下午1 点是 Stata 32的 两个方式
three the next lecture next week will be
下周将有三个下一个讲座
on deep learning for a sense in the
关于深刻学习的感觉
human understanding the human and we
人类了解人类和我们
will release online only lecture on
将仅 在线发布讲座
capsule networks and Gans general
胶囊网络和甘斯将军
adversarial networks thank you very much
对抗网络非常感谢你
[Applause]
[掌声]